

+8801626889595

shariarsaimon41@gmail.com

Ka-5/C, Jagannathpur,

Bashundhara R/A, Dhaka

Linkedin.com/in/shariar-islam-

LANGUAGES

C
C++

DART

PYTHON

JAVA SCRIPT

ENGLISH

REFERENCE

MD Rafiqul Islam Managing Director, Saimon Properties Ltd. & +8801712182967

Mr Ahnaf Abid CEO of QuickMed & +8801612946622

HOBBIES









Shariar Islam Saimon

Application Designer & Developer

Self dependent and organized individual with Bachelor's degree with honors in Computer Science and Engineering seeks admission into Master's program in Computer Science to advance technical expertise on Machine Learning and application development. After completion of Post-graduation, I want to be associated with a dynamic and progressive organization that will allow me to utilize my abilities and qualifications in the field to add value to the organization while providing me with opportunities for growth. Eventually implement with all the experience towards my father's real estate Company.

EXPERIENCE

2020 - PRESENT | APP DEVELOPER | QUICKMED

Basically, it's a startup business initialized by a group of my university including me as an app developer. We started our journey with the two-semester long period of planning and execution and displayed it in our Capstone. We took the professional step onward, I am in charge in the development and testing of the mobile application, executing new modules and regularly fix and update bugs in the live hosted platform.

2020 - PRESENT | GENERAL MANAGER | SAIMON PROPERTIES LTD

I have started as an IT specialist in the company, I myself developed and deployed the website of the company. Currently working on a ERP software for the company, in short it will work as an e-office. Besides, I have been the admin of the social platforms and generating leads. Recently, being the General Manager I have been active in the marketing and advertisement of the company and its projects.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering North South University, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Major: CSE (Computer Science and Engineering)

CGPA: 3.24

Relevant Coursework: Machine learning, Artificial Intelligence, Internet and web technology, Database Management System, Software engineering.

2012 - 2014 A' Levels

Hurdco International School, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Curriculum: Cambridge (CIE)

SKILLS

Android/IOS Development Web Development Application Design

Machine Learning & Al HTML/CSS Team Work

Digital Marketing Photoshop/illustrator Mathematics

ACTIVITIES

- Working on an ERP software for a real estate company (Saimon Properties Ltd.).
- Got Certified from Creative It Institution upon completion of Web Development course.
- Alumni member at North South University Computer and Engineering club(NSU CEC).
- Daily Star Awardee of excellent result in A' levels 2013-14
- Freelancing in local citation for hotels in USA, Canada
- Teaching experience of more than 5 years (O' Levels and A' Levels).
- Voluntering in Youth Wave Foundation (2014).